Thank you for watching!
Good evening, ladies and gentlemen.
What's up?
Once.
You say it with me.
Yes, sir.
What?
Gentlemen.
It's not a question of saying it, it's a question of saying it.
I don't know if it's okay to say it.
It's fine.
What?
The morning chime.
The morning chime has rung.
We're the CJs.
I, Kunitake, will be your host for today.
I'll bring it to you.
I thought that's what I was supposed to do.
You scared me.
Well, well, well.
Yes, sir.
Yes.
I'm Kashiwagi Nata, collection number 10.
Pleased to meet you.
Yes, ma'am.
Attendance number 14, I'm Karano Kunimo.
I greeted you earlier.
It's important every time, isn't it?
Attendance number 15, I am Nanoka Fusui. I look forward to working with you.
Yes, I am. Then, let's begin.
Okay. This is the 45th showroom of the EBICHU.
Yes, thank you very much for watching the 45th EBichu's Delightful and Frivolous Showroom today.
Thank you very much.
Yes, Ebichu's Delightful and Frivolous Showroom is the sister show of our sister show, Ukka-san's showroom.
Yes.
Yes, Ebichu's showroom is the original avatar of our showroom,
The original avatar of Ebichu's showroom is available by registering to the showroom,
You can get it by giving free or paid gifting.
Yes, I know.
You are flying.
I'm flying!
Well, I'm going to make a riking announcement.
First.
I'm worried about today!
I'm a little scared. Are you okay?
I'm scared.
From the 5th.
From 5th place.
Fifth place, Mr. Iwaki.
Thank you very much.
Fourth place, Mr. Monta.
3rd, Omie-san.
Thank you very much.
2nd place, Po-chan Ega-san.
1st place, Tamamin-san.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much. As I said before,
The original avatar for the Ebituaries Showroom is the showroom.
I said it, so skip it...
Yes, sir.
It's fine.
There are a lot of them.
Wait a minute.
What happened today?
Are you okay?
Are you okay? Yuna.
Yuna, have you ever MC'd before?
No, I haven't.
It's my first time.
Last time Yuna and the others were on the stage.
When Yuna and her friends were on the stage, we were numbered 1, 2, and 3.
Coconner did it.
Yuna followed Coconner.
Today it's Yuna's turn to pull.
Because it's my turn too.
With the two of you.
I don't have much to do at the top.
I've never done it before.
It's the first time.
I'll go with Yuna today.
I'll follow you.
I'll be right behind you.
There are a lot of people here.
They want you to do your best, Yuna.
Yuna-chan, you should take it at your own pace.
I'll do my best for my first MC.
Yes, I'll do my best for my first MC. You have many avatars.
Yes, I have a lot of avatars.
I wrote a lot of avatars.
I see.
If you click on the Twitter symbol on the screen
you can spread the word about this distribution on Twitter.
Please help us spread the word on Twitter.
Please help us.
So, this is
It's time to spread the word.It's time to spread the word.
To get this distribution to as many people as possible
to see this broadcast as many people as possible.
I'm going to tweet an announcement on Twitter
I'm going to tweet an announcement on Twitter.
Please retweet it.
What do you want me to do?
The retweet symbol?
I see what you mean.
This way?
Okay.
Thank you.
Does this look like a retweet symbol to you?
Retweet now?
Was it a square? It doesn't matter which one it is.
It doesn't matter. Okay, well, I'm sure you'll get a tweet soon, so please retweet me.
Yes, I can see it. But they'll see it. The retweet symbol. He says the idea is genius.
Thank you. It's not invisible.
Everyone is putting a "cute" stamp on it. What's that? It's true, they say it's cute, cute, cute.
Yes, we celebrated the 10th anniversary of our major label debut on May 5,
And you two, including COCONA, celebrated the first anniversary of joining EBICHU. Congratulations!
May 5th is the day when the distribution of "Seishun Zombies" started and the song is now playing.
On that day, we performed in Osaka during our spring tour, and many other things happened.
How do you feel after a year? Heh.
I don't know, but I have experienced many things, such as radio, filming, and many live performances, so it's been great.
I think it has been a year of growth for me, and I am looking forward to the second live tour this year.
There are many more shows coming up, so I hope I can grow even more.
What do you think, Yuno-chan? Yuno-chan, you've started to MC as well. It's true.
I used to be able to speak only a little, but now I think I can speak in a proper voice.
But I think we have all grown a lot, both of us. Thank you very much.
I know that some of you probably came to the May 5th meeting, so do you think that the new members have grown a lot over the past year? If so, please give us your comments.
Of course, there have been a lot of lessons and live performances, so you can see it visibly, but is there anything that you like about the new members?
Everyone has become more mature.
Is that so? This one.
The singing has gotten so much better.
I think their faces and facial expressions have become more attractive. Not during the live performance?
I used to sing along with the songs, but after seeing the spring tour this past year, I think I've gotten better at it.
I used to only think about the choreography and singing of the song during the live, but now I have more time to look around me, or perhaps I am able to look around me.
It's true. I am now able to pick on my seniors.
I can do that, you know.
You call your senpai "cows,
That's right.
You called me a cow.
It took me 5 minutes,
For the release of the newly-released album "Private Evistuak", I played the theme of stopping the timer in exactly 5 minutes,
I played the theme of stopping the timer in exactly five minutes, and we talked about the theme,
Mire-chan suddenly suggested doing Magical Banana.
And then we had five minutes.
I see. I see.
So, what was it again?
I wonder why she said cow.
What was it?
When I said cow, I was talking about Hinata-chan.
I said cow, and Yuko said cow,
I asked her why,
She said, "You wear a lot of cow-patterned clothes.
I didn't.
I asked her later and she said it was zebra.
I see.
He thought the zebra print was a cow.
A cow.
But, you know, I think all three of us have a lot of growing up to do,
We are still in the middle of our spring tour,
Next week is Carrier in Aichi, right?
There was the Sapporo show the other week, and the Ibaraki and Cocona outing, and so on.
There was a performance in Sapporo, Ibaraki, and Cocona,
I'm from Chiba Prefecture, but I've never had the concept of performing outside of Japan,
I am also from Chiba Prefecture, but I never really felt like I was back in Chiba,
So, for the first time, I will be performing in Aichi next week.
But of course, I am from Tokyo, and there are many things I do in Tokyo on a daily basis,
I don't say "I'm back" when I come back to Tokyo,
I won't say "I'm back.
I'm not going to say "I'm back" because I'll be back in Tokyo. That's why I was wondering if Yuu will be in Aichi next week.
Everyone said congratulations.
Yes, I'm looking forward to it. I'm looking forward to it.
I'm looking forward to it, but I'm nervous because it's in Aichi.
It's because it's in my hometown.
Cocona is acting weird.
I was so nervous.
She was so nervous right up to the start of the show.
It was different from usual.
But the audience seemed to be having a great time and said "Tadaimaima" (I'm home).
Yuko was also in Aichi.
I'm home. I can finally go back to Aichi.
Yuno came to Tokyo after high school, so she lives with her mother,
So it really feels like going home.
That's right. I'm going home.
I'm sure there will be people who will come for the spring tour.
I'll be waiting for you in Aichi.
I'm so glad.
Do you have any recommendations for sightseeing? I'm going to Aichi Park.
I don't have any. Aichi.
You said you don't have any.
There isn't.
I thought about it a lot, but I couldn't come up with anything.
I thought that maybe it's because there are so many places to play that it's not so great because it's my hometown.
This is the first time for us to do a live concert in Kalia.
We always play in Nagoya.
I don't know.
But I don't know...the food and all,But, you know, food,
I always bring delicious local delicacies for this spring tour,
I always get some delicious local delicacies brought to my dressing room,
What do you think?
Hikimabushi?
Oh, Nagoya.
I want some!
Nagoya?
Nagoya.
Is Aichi OK?
And Miso-nikomi Udon noodles, too.
I want to eat it!
I sure do!
Nagoya.
There are a lot of Nagoya foods, but...
Misen, for example.
Tebasaki (chicken wings).
Certainly.
Taiwanese ramen.
I wondered why Taiwanese ramen is in Aichi.
Even though it's called Taiwan.
I wonder why.
Is it the same thing as Tokyo Disneyland in Chiba?
Indeed.
They have a lot of things in Chiba.
Tokyo German Village.
Indeed! It's not Tokyo!
It's neither Tokyo nor Germany.
There are a lot of things like that.
I wonder what it is.
Fun. What will we be able to eat?
Because it's still going on.
For now, this week, this week?
On the 28th.
I'll be there for the placement.
Please come. Let's have fun together.
Let's have fun together.
Wait a minute. I'm starting to spin?
I've been thinking.
I'm sorry about that.
But not yet, not yet.
Not at all.
Like the mental zombies,
The streaming's running right now.
I'm starting to work on it.
Oh, my God. It's tough.
Yes, it is. Mental Zombies.
The Mental Zombies are now available for download.
The song that's playing right now.
Have you heard it?
Are you listening? Everybody?
Are you listening?
I'm also involved in a project
I'm also involved in a project to count the number of times it has been played.
On the LINE MUSIC site.
I wrote that it has reached 10 million views.
Today. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
It's a really fun song.
It's a song that makes me feel like summer has started.
Summer.
There's also "Ebi Iro" and "I'm in love with you.
It's pretty much about Ebichu.
I don't know what it has to do with
I don't know.
I was listening to it,
I see.
You wrote the song for "Hai Tate Ki" and "Beni".
Takuya, the former Julien Marie who wrote the song
who wrote "Beni no uta" (Red Song), wrote this song as well.
who wrote "Beni no uta" (Red Song), wrote it this time, too.
Really. It's like summer.
It's a bright pop song.
I can't wait to play it.
I want to play it.
Everyone wants to hear it live.
I think it would be a lot of fun to play it live.
There are a lot of balls and stuff.
It's going to be a lot of fun.
I'm looking forward to it.
They want to hear it at Famien.
We'll be playing at Famien, too.
Yes, the Famien.
I want to see it live.
It's going to be a lot of fun.
He said he thought we were going to do it in Ibaraki.
We've only done the distribution.
They haven't done it at all.
I want to do it.
I wonder if they will. I don't know.
I want to hear it in a medium tone.
A ballad.
A zombie song about youth.
A summer song.
Like a single piano.
I call them poetry zombies.
That's true.
That's great.
Sounds good.Looks good.
He said it might be good.
Medium tone version.
Ballad super zombie.
That's what it is.
He said he might cry if it's a mid-tone version.
I don't know if I'm really going to cry.
It sounds like an emotional song.
Well, it sure does.
Bossa nova version
There could be a bossa nova version.
Various versions are possible.
I think there will be zombies in Chichibu.
Zombies in Chichibu.
Zombies?
Zombies.
I wonder if there will be.
Well, it's time to move on.
I guess you didn't get the live ones.
That's enough.
Let's talk about Yuno today.
Don't you have anything you want to talk about?
I slept a lot today.
We talked about it earlier.
Today...
At 3:00 a.m.
I started working.
You've been living on the bed all day.
That's nice.
I went to school.
A student.
You're a student too.
Sort of.
You didn't go?
Not today.
I didn't have school.
But I've been having a lot of fun lately.
I've been having a lot of fun lately.
I slept a lot.
Yes, I did. I slept a lot.
I've been moving a lot.
Yesterday, I had a talk session
I had a talk session and an InstaComm distribution.
I told you about this at Lilly Way.
I told you about it at Lilyway.
music video.
It was a very fast day.
I hope you enjoy it.
The song is still a secret.
I won't tell you.
I don't say, "Enjoy the show.
I was just having fun, you know.
Really.
It didn't feel like a music video shoot.
We were just having fun.
It was fun.
It was like we were just playing together.
Please look forward to it.
Looking forward to it.
So.
I'll ask the users what they're up to.
What are you guys up to?
What did you do?
What did you do today?
What's going on?
Anything?
I enjoyed the talk.
And the trade fair.
It was our first time.
Online Trade City.
It was fun.
I was working.
Everyone was working.
Thanks for your hard work.
It's Monday, right?
The beginning of the week.
It's the beginning.
I heard you had a midterm test.
It's just now.
The first test of the next semester.
The first test.
A test.
Because Non-chan is?
She's taking a test?
She's a student.
I don't have time. What do you think you're going to do?
I haven't studied at all.
You've been doing it all right.
Yesterday, I was working on an assignment I had to submit.
I didn't think it was finished.
I never do it after I get home.
I was going to do it.
You're sitting next to Yoon-ho on your cell phone.
I'm telling you the truth. I was looking at my phone.
I have an assignment coming up.
Are you okay with the deadline?
I'm fine. I'll do it today.
Really?Really?
You declared to your mother that you'll do it tomorrow.
I have an early day tomorrow.
That's true.
But I'll do the assignment today.
You're going to do it.
So you're leaving?
But I'll do my assignment now, too.
I'm going to do the assignment while watching.
Can you do the assignment while watching?
Can you do it?
To the song.
You said, "Let's get rid of the homework.
Absolutely not.
He said, "You had time this morning.
I was asleep.
You were sleeping.
That's true.
The three of us are so different from each other.
This is what I'm talking about.
That's true.
Cocona is the type to go out unexpectedly.
Yuno stays at home all the time.
That's true.
I liked Yuuno the best.
Is Cocona close to Yuuno? I wonder.
But not Yuuno. Yuno turns off the lights in her room from morning till night.
She turns off the lights in her room? Don't you want to turn on the lights? Should I turn off the lights here, too?
It's pitch-dark. I don't know, do you think it's better to broadcast in total darkness?
That's okay. It's fine.
Then you won't fall asleep? Are you okay with that?
I slept a lot today, so I'm fine. That's right.
Sleep a lot. That's right, that's right.
I like the bumpy balance between the three of us.
Oh, really.
When we do our assignments, we are also divided into different types, aren't we?
This one goes to a café to study.
That's true.
Nonaka does hers when there's a restaurant open.
What about Yu?
You don't do it anytime, do you?
I don't do it anytime.
He was there. He was here.
You always don't do it.
My pace.
Are you a last-minute kind of person?
The same.
Assignments are always last minute, right? Do you feel motivated?
No, I don't.
Don't ask me about homework.
Ayaka was in the same grade as me, and she was doing it, but I watched her.
But I guess Yuu was in that category, too.
I couldn't do all of them.
I couldn't do everything.
That's why Mirei taught me a lot.
She would teach me things.
I thought Mirei-chan was great because she taught others while doing her own work.
At that time, Mirei-chan was also in college, and even though we went to high school together, Mirei-chan taught me things that I didn't understand.
I thought Mirei-chan was great.
He was amazing.
There are people who say they don't give assignments.
I don't.
From now on, I'm going to have Hinata-chan teach me.
This is something I have to learn too.
I can't do anything weird.
I can't do anything weird...I can't do it if there's an X or something.
I can't do anything more than addition.
Addition.
I was fast only in 100-square math.
What is 100-square math?
Era? You know what it is, don't you?
Don't you know?
100s?
Wait a minute. We're all at 100% of Generation 100 here.
Hey, you all know the 100-square math, right?
What? What do you mean?
Are you kidding me?
Wait a minute. Is there a generation barrier here? I haven't seen the three of you before...
And you draw diagonally?
I don't think so.
What?
I don't know Mr. Million Helpers.
But there are a lot of people who don't know.
What? This isn't from that time period or anything, right?
Eh? No? What do you mean?
Can you draw it diagonally?
Do we only work in Chiba?
What kind of unit is it?
It says we only do Chiba.
If it's like this,
I can draw here and here, and here and here.
Yes, you can draw more and more diagonally like this.
So that's how it is.
I have never done that.
No, I haven't.
I heard that there was no such thing in Aichi Prefecture.
What?
Does it depend on the prefecture?
Is the "million helpers" different in each prefecture?Is the "million helpers" different for each prefecture?
It says Osaka will do it too.
What?
Niigata has it. I know Shizuoka.
I don't know if they do it in Aichi.
Ibaraki didn't have it either.
I'm in the same grade as Yuno and she said they did.
Wait, Yuno?
Wait a minute.
But you don't know anything about it either, do you?
I don't know.
That's scary.
It's a bit of a strange place to come out.
Of course.
You guys are students, right?
You want to follow me? I'm going to start with you two.
Can I ask you to teach me something next time, Million Helpers?
I'll only teach you million helpers.
I'll only teach you to help millionaires.
Okay, I'll go next.
Okay.
Okay, so today we're going to do a project like this.
It's called, "Hilarious and hilarious audition.
Yay!
Okay, here are the rules.
As announced on May 5, we are currently looking for new members,
We are looking for new members,
We're accepting applications until June 10,
Please check the official website for details.
Yes, we are looking for new members.
You are going to hold an audition for new members, right?
Yes.
What do you think?
But, you know, we've been here a year now,
Soon to be seniors,
I mean, we're going to be seniors,
Maybe,
We're 10 to 22 years old, right?
That's right.
So I'm older than both of them,
But there is a possibility that someone who is older than the two of us, but junior in terms of history, will join us,
Can you teach them well?
Oh, my God,
You're doing a great job.
I'm using honorifics now.
No, I'll probably start with 7. I'm sure they'll teach you well.
I'm not very good at teaching.
I can't express myself in words,
The more I ask, the less I understand.
Really?
What's going to happen to Coconner?
I think Coconar will be a strict senior.
The kind of person who teaches hard,
He might become a spartan senior who teaches hard.
He's also a hard-ass to Mino.
Like Arechi.
No, I think he's spartan with me, too.
At first, I wanted to tell him.
I really prefer it this way.
But thanks to that,
Yuno has become softer.
I also became softer.
So, even if a hard girl comes in,
Even if a hard girl comes in, we have Coconner,
You don't have to worry about that.
Yuuno has softened too.
I'll be fine.
I'm going to say this for the first time in the showroom,
This December,
I will be transferring from Ebichi this December,
I'm not able to do this audition now,
I can't be active right now,
But I will probably go to a camp or something while I'm here,
I have a lot of auditions coming up,
I'll also have to be a little more strict with my legs.
Okay, Yuno is also wearing a full-body black corset.
That's my last year's.
But they don't have showrooms anymore.
But, you know, we don't know what kind of girls will come in.
I'm just thinking about how much I want to join Ebichu,
I don't know how many of them are interested in joining EBITCHU and are applying for the audition.
I don't know.
What kind of kids do you want?
What kind of girl?
I'd like a girl who is kind and easy to get along with.
Gentlemen.
What if a girl who looks like a gal comes in?
More than Cocona.
I'll try to get along with her, but I might not be able to keep up with her.
I might not be able to keep up with them.
I think the person who joins us is probably a kind person.
Okay, then.
So, as we did at the last audition, we will be holding auditions for new members here in the showroom as well,
We would like to hold an audition for new members in this showroom as well.
We are open to all genders and ages, so please leave your comments,
We will be hiring on the spot.
We will be hiring on the spot,
So, everyone, please keep on promoting yourselves.Then everyone, please keep on promoting yourselves.
Please do.
I think I'll audition too.
You have until June 5th, right?
What name should I use?
What should I do? What name should I use?
Because Nanaie Kashiwagi can't do it anymore.
If I was going to talk yesterday, it would be "Hoshi no Mirai".
That's right.
I thought I'd go with Hoshi no Mirai because I can't go with Hoshi no Mirai, which is more like Mirei,
But I'm 23 years old, so I'm out,
So I cheated a little and made her born in 2000,
I said, "I'm going to be 22,
But I was thinking that the day of the audition and interview would be the day of the concert,
But I was thinking that the day of the audition interview would be the day of the concert, so I would have to miss the concert.
I'm sure of it.
I'll have to cancel the live show for the new member audition.
Yes, that's right.
But a lot of people are coming.
Mirai, the star.
If I enter the universe, I can serve soft serve ice cream well.
Don't worry, I can do it by myself.
I'm unhappy right away.
Oh, I wonder what it is.
I wonder what it is.
I'm good at eating chicken wings.
How's it going? - It's not bad, is it?
Is that a boo?
Boo.
I can drive a car.
It would be great to have more cars.
Yeah, that would be great.
Thank you.
I passed
Thank you!
I'll be your personal pastry chef!
I can eat sweet and savory desserts every day!
I prefer something a little salty.
I'm sorry.
That's great.
That's tough. That's pretty tough.
I don't know.
I'll carry your bag. He'll carry your bag or something.
I feel a little sorry about that.
I feel sorry, so it's no good.
It's no good.
I'll do my best not to make the network unstable during the delivery.
That's good.
That's good. Congratulations.
The love of the shrimpers will not be outdone.
Oh wow.
We're stronger than you.
Well, well, well. Well, then, we didn't pass.
I wonder what it is.
They want to take pretty pictures of the members.
Oh, wow.
What do you think?
Maru? Maru? Maru.
Yes, sir.
Heh.
What is it?
What is it? What? What?
What did you say yes to?
I said yes to what?
And I pressed it at the same time.
Oh, nothing.
We were just playing.
You're so different from today's MC.
Is everything okay?
I don't know.
I'm carrying around a big bag of groceries Oh, no problem, I'll lend you the money for a charge Oh, that's great, thank you
I'll help you with your assignment, that's great, I want 10 more
I'll farm oysters, Cocona will love that
I don't know
I'll be Yuno's interpreter
You know what I'm talking about...
I made homemade dumplings! So cute!
Hina-chan, will you do it too?
We'll get you a sauna. But will they like it?
Ayama-san, Ayachan, Hina and Mire-chan.
I'll be your bodyguard. I'm a better bodyguard than you, but I want it.
That's why I made it round.
I'll do bodywork every day. Bodywork?
Bodywork? Massage?
You need it?
Are you okay?
Then I don't need one.
If you bring me to the younger one, I'll bring you one too.
I'll bring you Anpanman chocolates every day.
Thank you.
Let's bring in lots of new members.
Lots and lots of new members.
I'll give you a wake-up call.
Thank you.
I'll take it.
I thought wake-up calls were supposed to wake me up.
I wake myself up.
My mom wakes me up.
Yeah.
I've never done it before.I've never done that before.
Can't you get up?
I'm gonna get butt hurt.
But you know what, I take a lot of pictures too.
I take a lot of pictures.
When I go to bed, I put myself in sleep mode.
So you don't know what's going on.
You don't have to put yourself in sleep mode.
That's right.
You're right.
I see.
I wonder...
I'll turn up the temperature in the lesson room.
No, you can't.
I'll find some local delicacies to eat.
You'll eat?
I'm going to eat.
I want some too.
I'll be there, Rino.
Thank you very much.
Yes, ma'am.
I'll write the members' blogs for them.
I'll write it for you.
But if I stop, you'll have to do it for me.
What? I'll get you a caterer.
I'll look for the earphones.
I'll look for my lost earphones.
They were in the bottom of my bag.
I don't lose my phone every day these days.
You look for it every day? Lost? Really?
Today I thought I lost my lipstick, but it was on the fridge.
All kinds of things.
You lost your comb, too.
It was right there.
I don't even know why I put it there.
I don't know why.
Where is it?
I'll find its mouth.
I'll look for it.
What do you think?
I'll get some yakisoba bread.
I want some!
Yakisoba for sunrise.
He's taking me to a barbecue restaurant.
I'll take you.
I'll go!
I'll give you New Year's money.
I will!
I'll advertise on TikTok.
I'm so happy!
I'll bring a gorilla!
Oh!
Mmm, I'm going to walk looooong with Po-chan.
Already.
I'll give you the missing change.
Change?
Oh, that's good.
I'll make dumplings.
Thank you very much.
I'll introduce you to a cute bird.
Bird? Bird?
I'll give you Christmas presents for 10 years.
It should be Christmas every day.
I'm going to get so many gifts.
I'm going to do coconut gals.
We can't have any more gals.
Yes, Yuna will be a little frightened.
I'll win the lottery.
That's great.
I'll protect Mirei's legs so they don't get caught.
Mirei's legs are a little long.
Oh, that's nice.
I'll praise her a lot.
Motive, motive, motive.
I'm going to buy Anpanman chocolates.
We'll end up with a lot of Anpanman chocolates.
I'll buy a house.
A house?
You mean an Ebichu house?
Sounds like fun.
I'll do the thick stuff instead.
Is that okay?
Isn't it hard to do? You're on your own.
I want to.
I'll take you to and from work every day.
Was that a grass art, too?
I'm buying a car.
I've become a fan of kusagei.
I'm buying a frying pan for Kamiyashiki.
Coconan will be happy.
What's that? She says she'll play games with me anytime.
But that's okay.
But okay, okay, okay.
Well, well, well.
Sometimes.
Miso soup.
Miso soup is delicious.Miso soup is delicious.
But aren't you happy?
It makes me happy.
I drink a lot before a concert.
You're really pushing it, aren't you?
She said she does nails on a daily basis.
Oh, wow.
No, I only have my pinky finger done.
Why do you only do your pinky finger?
Just before, I thought, oh, I forgot.
I just painted it right before Ibaraki Park.
Only your pinky?
Yes, I do it once a month.
I do a tacopan once a month.
Wow, that's nice.
He said he would help me if I almost forgot the lyrics. Oh, thank you so much.
Remember! Memorize it! Memorize it, memorize it!
I'm adopting it now. Hey.
How many have you hired? I don't even know anymore.
I've been doing it for a long time. What if we end up with 100 people in the shrimp group?
The last one. Can I be the last one?
Okay, okay, okay. Okay, just let it go.
Do you have any?
I'll get you some gummies.
It's just Yu no more.
They're Yu's.
That's Yoo's!
You get attendance number 100.
Oh, no.
Then, how about the total?
Yes.
Great, you wrote it down.
Two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten, 11, 12.
Twelve?
I'll be damned.
That's a first.
I've never had someone write and show me their voice.
Yu no, Yu no-chan is going wild today.
Twenty-eight recruits.
She's a candidate for the center.
What do you think?
What do you think? Are there any? A candidate for the center?
I don't know.
Someone who can drive a car would be nice.
That's very realistic.
That makes me want another car for Emi.
I don't have anyone to buy me a car.
That's for sure.
That's the thing.
If we had another car, we would have three cars,
That's true.
The members will be divided into 3, 3, 3, and so on.
We're all pretty tightly packed right now.
Usually, it's 2, 3, 2, 2.
But, to be realistic, this is the best.
That's for sure. That's good. It's a good network.
People who can stabilize the distribution network,
I want that.
You want it the most?
I want it the most.
Even if they start distribution all of a sudden.
That's exactly what you did after the Osaka show on May 5, right?
Insta?
YouTube.
YouTube?
It got really bad during the streaming,
The staff was in a panic.
Fuji and all, and they looked so upset,
Fuji, and they had to go outside and inside,
It was very hard work, and so were the people watching,
It was an important presentation,
Fuji, and they had to go outside and inside, and it was really hard work,
I think it was a big problem, you know.
I heard it was a bad broadcast.
That's right.
So let's be realistic about this,
What is important from now on is
The person who stabilizes the distribution network.
As a candidate for the center, what is your attendance number?
What number do you want for the center candidate?
What number?
About 15.
About 20?
No, there are about five people in the room when I close it.
That's quite a lot.
Oh, I see.
But it doesn't matter what number you are.
Let's call the attendance number, Hatena number.
Huh?
Oh, number 0?
Number 0 is good.
Number 0?
Zero.
I'll take that as a "Pass".
Pass. Are you sure about that?
Are you sure?
No, but, well..,
Oh, well, well, well,Oh well,
Mmm,
Uh, I don't know what to do.
I'm not sure,
I'm going to say that we all failed.
After all, after all.
I'm lost.
I want it, but..,
Yes, I do.
I'd like you to audition for it,
I'm sure you're right.
You have until June 10 to apply,
We are accepting applications until June 10,
We would appreciate it if you could give us a lot of applications.
I hope to see many of you there.
Okay, that's all. Well, that's all,
That's all for now.
Thank you very much.
Okay, bye,
Okay.
Okay, this is the 45th edition of EBICHU's Delightful and Frivolous Showroom,
It's coming to an end in the blink of an eye.
That was fast.
So fast.
Yeah, it was.
How was it?
MC.
It wasn't me.
It was almost like I was the one talking,
It was you.
The MC.
It was me.
No, it was me,
We'll have a review meeting later.
At the review meeting.
Yes, that's right.
It might end up here.
I might get really angry.
But it was the first time I did a showroom with you two,
It was the first time.
It was really fun.
It's so lively.
It's lively and fun.
It was good.
Surprisingly, being with the older sister members,
Of course, it's fun and I'm excited,
But they are not so fresh.
They are not so fresh.
They are a little more relaxed,
But you two are fun.
Really?
I'm glad.
I hope you continue to have fun.
Yes, we are.
I'm looking forward to it.
Well then, I'm going to make an announcement.
Yes, I will.
An announcement.
You wrote them, Hina-chan.
First of all, I forgot to write some of them. I just thought of it now.
I just thought of it.
I haven't written anything. Let's start with the ones you have written.
It was announced the other day,
Shiritsu Ebisu Chugaku major debut 10th Anniversary 2MANZEPP TOUR
Houkago Rock'n'Roll" will be held from July to October.
It will run from July to October,
We are going to play "Ebisu Chugaku 10-ban",
We will be playing against each other.
The artist and his/her partner will be announced at a later date,
We will announce the artist and his/her partner at a later date,
Please look forward to it,
July 21 and 22 at ZEPP Nagoya,
July 21 and 22 at ZEPP Nagoya, July 25 and 26 at ZEPP Haneda, and August 22 and 23 at ZEPP Haneda,
ZEPP Haneda on July 21 and 22, ZEPP Osaka on July 25 and 26, August 22 and 23, and ZEPP Osaka on September 1 and 2,
ZEPP Osaka on September 1 and 2, and ZEPP Diver City on October 17 and 18.
The fan club advance registration is
The fan club advance order will be accepted until 23:59 on the 29th of this month.
I'm looking forward to it.
This is what I said, I'm going to do a lot of live shows throughout this year,
I really have 10 gigs,
I wonder who I'm going to play with.
I wonder who he's going to play with.
I'm looking forward to it.
You can apply before the fans know who you're going to play with.
That's true.
Thinking positively.
Normally, I would tell them that I'm going to do it with them before accepting the application,
But you accepted the application without saying so.
They already applied.
Thank you very much.
I hope you are looking forward to it.
And now, it's playing.
The 10th anniversary of Berryz Chugakko's major debut.
So, 10 contents release.
So, for the month of May, "Youth Zombies" is being distributed.
It's playing now, isn't it?It's flowing now.
Like March and April,
Anytime Anywhere,
Happy End Then and There,
But from now on, from June, we are going to continue to distribute them until December,
From now on, from June, and still until December,
We will be releasing something from June to December,
So please look forward to it,
The next one will be in June.
You have already finished recording the song for June,
Yes, it's very cute.
It is very cute.
It's a nice song.
Cute is fine.
It's a very cute and fun song,
Please enjoy it.
I haven't written anything about it yet,
We are currently on our spring tour,
Next stop is Aichi on the 28th.
Next stop is Aichi on the 28th, at Kalia.
I'm going to play at Kalia,
We still have tickets available for Tochigi Koen and Fukuoka Koen,
Please come and join us.
Please come.
And on August 6th and 7th, Saturday and Sunday.
The Fami-en will be held on Saturday and Sunday, August 6th and 7th.
Yes.
We can finally do the Fami performance.
It's the first time. I am very happy.
We will be performing at the Yamanakako Koryu Plaza Kirara Theater Hibiki.
It's been 3 years since you've performed at Famien.
Yes, we haven't done it since 2019,
It's been a long time since we've had a Fami performance,
I hope everyone can make memories of the summer with us.
We will be holding auditions for new members until the 10th of June and we are looking for new members.
If you would like to join us as a member of Ebichu, we would love to have you,
We are looking for people who want to work together as Ebichu and we would love to have you as a member,
We are looking forward to hearing from you.
We are waiting for your application.
I guess that's about it.
So, this is the end of the 45th edition of EBICHU's fun and funny showroom.
And an important announcement.
The next broadcast will be on June 7 at 20:00.
The next episode will include a review meeting, so please check it out.
We will resume in a few minutes, so please stay tuned.
And now, the final ranking.
Yukitsun-san comes in 5th place. Thank you very much.
4th place, Po-chan Ega-san. Thank you very much.
3rd place, Mr. Monta. Thank you very much. 2nd place, Tamamin-san. Thank you very much. 1st place, Mr. Kouhei Hokkaido. Thank you very much.
Well, now that we've moved on, please comment if you have anything you would like to tell us in the review session.
Well, we will end the distribution once, but we will resume soon. Well, that's all for now.
CJB was the star of the show.
Bye bye. Thank you very much. Watch this later.
YUNO WORLD. Yuno said it's interesting.
They are swamped in Yunop's world.
He wants to see Yuno's solo show.
I wonder if Yoon-ho will be okay with his solo performance.
I don't think so.
I wonder if it's okay for me to watch.
Let's do it next time, shall we?
It's started?
It's started.
Thank you for your hard work.
How was the MC?
It was difficult.
Was it difficult?
Me too, I did it before.
It was difficult.
It's difficult.
How is it? How was it from your point of view?
MC
MC?
Yes.
I was MCing!
I thought I was the MC today.
Was it me?
Yes, it was.
Not yes.
No, but...
YU-NO is interesting.
YU-NO's worldview is so strong.
It's definitely not like any other distribution.
It's the only one that's impossible to deliver.
I've never seen anyone with such a strong view of the world.
I'm sure you'll never get tired of watching it.
You never know what's going to happen.
I could go off on a crazy tangent.
Or go to a different place.
Or suddenly there's a punch that's really strong and straight
There are a lot of things like that.
But that's what makes it fun.
And it's fun to come back suddenly.
I think it's good.
I think it's nice.
but I was worried about the delivery after I left the shrimp
I wonder if someone could put it together for me.
I'm sure someone will put it all together, but I'm not sure.
I know he's trying so hard to get back today.I saw Nonaka trying so hard to bring it back today.
Nonaka and Zaimoto.
Nonaka and I were looking at the book of materials.
I was telling him, "Here it is.
I thought I had it all together now.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It was a negotiation.
He did this for me.
I'm sure Nonaka can handle this.
I'll do my best.
Thank you.
Anything goes in the showroom.
I don't know if I'm a good MC or not.
I don't know if I'm a good MC or a bad MC, but I think it's okay to have this kind of show.
The only one who has a script at least...
Kunimom-san is the only one who has a script.
After saying "Good evening, everyone.
I don't know what you two are talking about.
It's true that it says "Private Ebisu Tube" once, but...
For example, I said, "I'm going to say it then.
I thought it would be nice if you could say something like "Se-no" or something like that.
That's what I was thinking.
It's a live broadcast, so it's not going to go on.
That's about it.
The rest is up to you.
I think it's fine if you do it.
I just wanted to push it at the same time as Tsuka Marukawa, you know?
I think it's a little confusing.
But I wanted to press them at the same time.
I'll have to give it a try.
It's been a while since I've been here for a serious reflection.
It's funny, on the contrary, it's funny now.
That's about right. That's about right.
I'm like, "Look at you guys, you're doing great." I'm like, "Yeah, I know.
I want to push it.
I'm sure you know what I'm talking about.
I'd like to push it a little bit.
I'm curious.
I wonder which one I'd get if I pressed both.
It was a circle. It's definitely a circle.
I don't know. Quickly. But you're right, I pushed a little too fast.
I got an "X".
But a circle is definitely a circle.
But I've never paid attention to this. It's a great point of view.
The button is there to be pushed.
That's philosophy. I want to push it.
It says "curiosity" in Japanese. It's a good episode.
It's a good episode.
So this is one of those times.
That's right.
Yes, I'll do my best.
I'll do my best not to get sidetracked again.
I'll do my best not to get hit. I'll do my best.
Then the MC will be responsible for the end.
That's right. I'm closing.
Please do.
Okay. Thank you very much.
Is that it?
Do you have anything more to say?
Thank you for watching. See you soon.
And don't forget to come back for our next showroom.
June 7th at 8:00.
Come see us again.